Adele Jenkins

424 Circle Place • Colorado Springs, CO 80905 • adelejenkins@aol.com • (719) 981-9801

Highly experienced Morning Show Anchor and Reporter with a proven track record for handling live interviews with ease

——————————————————————————————————————	
--	--

More than seven years' experience gained in commercial television news combined with a college degree. Popular with viewers and accessible; well-traveled with a genuine interest in a variety of subjects. Able to quickly gain the trust of sources and enterprise exclusive story ideas. Strong ability to stay calm and "think on feet" during equipment malfunctions. Compelling storyteller, fast typist with speed exceeding 60 WPM. Professional demeanor in the newsroom and the community. Highly knowledgeable about Colorado news, geography, and politics.

"Adele always brings great story ideas to the morning meeting and is genuinely nice to work with. She's always been helpful, gracious, and generous."

- Susan Geary, KRDO News Producer

Experience -

✓ Anchor

✓ Reporter

✓ Producer

✓ Emcee

✓ Host

✓ Writer

- ✓ Field Producer
- ✓ Assignment Editor
- ✓ Mode

Career Achievements —

Voted Best Anchor - The Independent • 2004

Helped Weekend News team win an Associated Press Award for *Breaking News* • 2002 Handled live coverage of the 2002 Blizzard which was entirely unscripted for four hours Recognized for *Commitment to Donation* by COPA for series reporting on *Organ Donations*

— Work History —

KRDO-TV/News 13 – Colorado Springs, CO

1999 - Present

Morning News Anchor / Co-host / Reporter for an ABC affiliate.

[2000 – Present]

- Write and help produce *Good Morning Colorado*, a two-hour program of live interviews, news, and cooking segments, along with cut-ins during ABC's *Good Morning America*.
- Anchor GMC "On the Road" several times per year throughout southern Colorado.
- Maintain excellent working relationships with production crews and producers to keep show on pace and seamlessly meet network programming.
- Report on a variety of topics for 5PM and 6PM newscasts, including *Parenting*, the *Spirit of Colorado Springs*, *Health Beat*, and hard news.
- Serve as a station representative within the community at fundraisers, auctions, and telethons, helping to break revenue records for Hospice and St. Jude.

Weekend News Anchor

[1999 - 2000]



SELF-EMPLOYED – Colorado Springs, CO *Family Manager*

1996 - 1998

KOAA-TV/Eyewitness News – Colorado Springs, CO

1994 - 1996

Reporter / Anchor / Producer / Assignment Editor at an NBC affiliate.

- Handled the weekend newscast, from planning and assigning coverage, to producing and anchoring show.
- Produced and hosted Concern, a taped public affairs program that aired daily.
- Wrote and edited multiple packages daily and reported live from planned events and breaking news.
- Served as fill-in Producer of the 5, 6 and 10PM newscasts.

KMGH-TV/7News – Denver, CO

1993 - 1994

Associate Producer of Daybreak at a CBS affiliate (now ABC.)

 Monitored feeds and viewed overnight video; edited PKGs to VO/SOTS; helped research background information, track sources, and write scripts.

KUSA-TV/9News – Denver, CO

1993

PT Associate Producer of the midday and evening newscasts at an ABC affiliate.

 Logged network feeds; wrote, separated, and distributed scripts; operated TelePrompTer.

Sports Intern [Spring 1993]

Telethons, Special Events, & Live Appearances

St. Jude Dream Home Telethon – Colorado Springs, CO • 2001 – Present Hospice Telethon – Colorado Springs, CO • 2001 – Present

Community Involvement ———

Pikes Peak Humane Society
Girl Scouts of America/Pikes Peak Troop
Team Captain – Bowl for Kids' Sake

- Technical Skills ——

AP NewsCenter • DMG • Pathfire • MS Windows 2000 • DVC Pro • Beta • Outlook

Education –

THE UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO – Boulder Bachelor of Arts in Broadcast Journalism • 1993







America's #1 Online Resume Builder

With Cover Letters

- Easy-to-use, guides you through step-by-step
- Resume templates, writing samples and tips
- One-click designs for the professional look you want
- Start from scratch or upload your resume



Already have an account?











Phone and Chat Hours: 7 Days a Week 6am to midnight EST



Write a resume - in minutes

Your resume is often your first and only chance to make a great impression on an employer. Managers will scan your resume for just 10 seconds to see if you're right for the job.

That's why your resume needs to be attractive and stand out. It needs to be well-written and highlight your skills to your best advantage.

The problem is most people don't know how to write a great resume and don't have the design skills to make it look professional.

- Our Resume Builder is designed to make resume-writing fast and easy.
- We match you with the right template and, in just one click, you can choose a professional design that will help you win the job.
- Our unique Text Tuner™ allows you to choose from hundreds of expert-written examples - no more writer's block!

Get the "most impressive resume builder on the market today". There's no risk; no obligation. We're so confident that you'll love our resume builder that you can try it for FREE.

According to our partners..."the most impressive resume builder on the market today."

onTargetiobs

YAHOO! hotjobs EmploymentGuide.com

Ret-Temps Joined

Customer Reviews

Job.com

"I was completely unaware of what companies are looking for in a resume. This product helped me word and format my professional resume and the examples were extremely useful. Overall, this is a great product. I would highly recommend these services." - A. Danihels

"This resume tool is so much better than templates - just upload or enter your resume content and you get your choice of designs. It's magical! Anyone can benefit from this tool: from students to executives!" - Belinda Yanda

View more reviews >









America's #1 Online Resume Builder

With Cover Letters

- Easy-to-use, guides you through step-by-step
- Resume templates, writing samples and tips
- One-click designs for the professional look you want
- Start from scratch or upload your resume



Already have an account?











Phone and Chat Hours: 7 Days a Week 6am to midnight EST



Write a resume - in minutes

Your resume is often your first and only chance to make a great impression on an employer. Managers will scan your resume for just 10 seconds to see if you're right for the job.

That's why your resume needs to be attractive and stand out. It needs to be well-written and highlight your skills to your best advantage.

The problem is most people don't know how to write a great resume and don't have the design skills to make it look professional.

- Our Resume Builder is designed to make resume-writing fast and easy.
- We match you with the right template and, in just one click, you can choose a professional design that will help you win the job.
- Our unique Text Tuner™ allows you to choose from hundreds of expert-written examples - no more writer's block!

Get the "most impressive resume builder on the market today". There's no risk; no obligation. We're so confident that you'll love our resume builder that you can try it for FREE.

According to our partners..."the most impressive resume builder on the market today."

onTargetiobs

YAHOO! hotjobs EmploymentGuide.com

Ret-Temps Joined

Customer Reviews

Job.com

"I was completely unaware of what companies are looking for in a resume. This product helped me word and format my professional resume and the examples were extremely useful. Overall, this is a great product. I would highly recommend these services." - A. Danihels

"This resume tool is so much better than templates - just upload or enter your resume content and you get your choice of designs. It's magical! Anyone can benefit from this tool: from students to executives!" - Belinda Yanda

View more reviews >



